RG 074:047, Elizabeth Dimmick Walters Genealogical Papers
Connecticut State Library
Elizabeth Dimmick Walters genealogical papers
1945-1975
Connecticut State Library
Walters, Elizabeth Dimmick
.75 cubic feet
Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, and genealogical notes on the Dimmick family.
RG074_047
1987-040
Scope and Content
Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, and genealogical notes on the Dimmick family.
Related Material
Dimmick, Dimmock family: History and Genealogy Unit Special Genealogical File, 1810-1882 Connecticut State Library
Index Terms
Persons:
Walters, Elizabeth Dimmick
Family Names:
Dimmick family
Places:
Connecticut -- Genealogy
Document Types:
Correspondence; Genealogies; Photographs; Clippings
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
The papers came to the Connecticut State Library in July 1987 from Elizabeth Dimmick Walters.
Container List
- Papers, 1945-1975
  - Correspondence letters to Mrs. Elizabeth (Dimmick) Walters, 1943-1968 (Box 1)
  - The History of the Ellen Battell Stoeckel Trust, Sydney Thompson, 1 bound volume (Box 1)
  - W.R. Webster, Connecticut, Birthplace of American Liberty, Birthplace of American Democracy, Home of Uncommon Men, An Appreciation, (Princeton University Press, 1945 ), 1 bound volume (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Historical Society Bulletin, 1950 January, volume 15, no. 1, 1 bound volume (Box 1)
  - GRIT Family Section, 1969 July 13, p. 36, 1 newspaper clipping (Box 1)
  - Dimmick (Dimock) family, 11 generations, 1 folder (Box 1)
  - Alford Storrs Dimick, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Dimmick (Dimock) genealogical notes, 1 folder (Box 1)
  - Dimmick-Ms, Box 1 & 2 - New England Historical and Genealogical Society, Boston, Mass. & other genealogical notes, 1 folder (Box 1)
  - Judge Edward Jordan Dimick & his ancestors, 1952-1953; 1 folder (Box 1)
  - W.H. Edwards, The Dimmick Family of Cape Cod, Mass. - Ancestors of John Edwin Robinson and his Sister Stella Adolphus Robinson, of Alabama, Louisiana and Texas, 1957, 1 notebook (Box 1)
  - Henry Burgess Lincoln Dimmick, 1951-1962; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Dimmick families of Falmouth, Mass., 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 2)
    Compiled from various sources.
  - Letters & family chart from Col. John Mesick of Natchez, Miss., 1963; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Edward Dimmick, 1950-1955; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Anna Dimmick, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Gideon Dimmick, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Dr. William Wallace Dimock, 1952-1955, 1975; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Descendants of Peter Dimmick & wife Elizabeth Chamberlin Dimmick, 1968; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Descendants of Augustus Right Dimmick, 1955-1967; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Dimmick family notes, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 2)
    Compiled by Kendall P. Hayward of Hartford, Conn. (Miscellaneous notes).
  - Descendants of Shubael Dimmick, Wales, Conn. & other Dimmick (Dimock) family notes, 1951-1958; 1 folder (Box 2)
    Compiled by Claude W. Barlow (Clark University, Mass.).
  - Sylvanus Dimmick & wife Thankful, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Descendants of Edward Dimmick & wife Ester Tilden, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 2)
  - Dimmick family notes, 1950-1953, 1967; 1 folder (Box 2)